(Sheldon:)...who have agreed to speak to you
on the phone right now.
Uh, Dr. Rostenkowski, Dr. Fowler?
Are you there?
(Amy(voice):)We're here.
Thank you for taking time out of your busy
schedule to enlighten these young women.
(Amy:)It's our pleasure.
(Amy:)I'm Dr. Fowler, and I'm a neuroscientist.
And I'm Dr. Rostenkowski-Wolowitz,
and I'm a microbiologist.
(Amy:)The world of science needs more women,
but from a young age...
(Amy:)...we girls are encouraged to care
more about the way we look...
(Amy:)...than about the power of our minds.
(Bernadette:)That's true. Every one of you has
the capacity to be anything you want to be.
Unless you wanna be Cinderella.
(Bernadette:)Come at me, see what happens.
(Raj(by text):)This was really fun.